9hive.com 2017-06-14

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting 9HIVE. The following is our privacy policy that describes our treatment of

information when you:

i. access to text, graphics, photographs, audios and videos

ii. access to 9HIVE links through its third party social media pages/accounts such as

Facebook®

iii. access to the site’s interactive features that enable you to connect with 9HIVE and its

other users

 **PLEASE READ THE PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE PROCEEDING TO THE SITE TO**

 **BE AN AUTHORIZED USER.**

 **Personal Information Collected**

Your personal information is provided to us by you as your identity as an individual user. To

utilize the Interactive Services on the site, you use your Facebook account. This allows us access

to your email address, the “About me” section, the “Likes” and the “Interests” section associated

with your account.

 **Use of Personal Information**

By submission of your personal information to us, you agree that we may share this data with:

i. a third party to bring you selected retail opportunities

ii. other companies working on our behalf, sending direct and electronic mails

iii. to provide you with customer service and to answer your queries

We also reserve the right to release your personal information:

i. if you violate our terms of use

ii. if we are acquired by some other company or get merged with it. In that case, you’ll be

informed via email

 **Interactive Services/Social Media Websites**

When you post a comment or feedback using your accounts on other social media sites, your

personal information will be visible to other users and can be used by them to contact you. We

are not responsible for the personal information that you submit with your consent on these

forums.

You also agree that 9HIVE is free to use your feedback without violating any social media

website’s terms and conditions.

 **Non-Personal Information Collection and Use**

 **IP Addresses/Browser Type**

9HIVE will have access to the kind of browser that you use (e.g.,Chrome, Internet Explorer),

your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the

domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Verizon, AT&T).

 **Cookies**

We assign cookies as your identity when you access the website to make your experience at the

site better. You have the choice to disable cookies.

 **Behavioral Tracking**

Cookies and other tracking technologies help us in recording your activities after you leave the

site. This is to understand the nature of advertisements that attract you. Third parties such as

Google ® may do similar tracking. While you cannot disable all of these, some may be disabled

by using the “Do Not Track” option in your browser.

 **Aggregate Data**

Aggregate or group data of the users can be used for lawful purposes.

 **Third-Party Websites**

The site may contain links to third party websites. When you get connected with any of these

websites via us, you have to follow the terms and conditions of that website. These websites may

ask for your personal information or credit card numbers. 9HIVE has no responsibility

regarding these websites that have their separate policies.

 **Security**

Your personal information is protected with us both online and offline.

 **Minors**

Users under 18 years of age are not encouraged to share their personal information on the site.

 **Deleting, Modifying and Updating Your Information**

We will delete, modify or update your information on your request. Deleting your personal

information will disable some features of the website for you. Your information may still remain

in your backup systems.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

The users will be notified about any change in the privacy policy.

 **For any further queries Fill out Form Below:**
